Guide to the Class of 1920, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Class of 1920, Yale College, records
1920-1983
RU 494
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.25
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, lists, photographs, and clippings documenting the reunions and members of the Yale College Class of 1920.
Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1920
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-A (YRG 10-A), Records of Yale College classes.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, lists, photographs, and clippings documenting the reunions and members of the Yale College Class of 1920.
Class reunions; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1920; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae
- Alumni information files, 1954-1983; Accession 1985-A-046
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2019
  - Alumni information: Correspondence, memoranda, lists, notices, diagrams, 1954-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alumni information: correspondence, memoranda, lists, fund, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: (1) 50th Class Reunion; (19) 60th Class Reunion [See also: YRG 48], 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Representative records: minutes, data, correspondence, clippings, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 35th Reunion, 1955 June 19-20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 50th Reunion, 1970 June 11-14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 55th Reunion, 1975 May 22-25 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 60th Reunion, 1980 May 30-31 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 61st Reunion, 1981 June 6 May 29? (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 63rd Reunion, 1983 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Photographs of the Class of 1920, Yale College, Accession 2007-A-069
  - Academic Class Day Committee, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - University Athletic Association Committee, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Senior Society?, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified group, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 1)